Guide to the Yale School of Music Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the dean of the Yale School of Music, 1994-2006; Accession 2007-A-092
  - Renovations
    - Leigh Hall -Plans Dean and Deans Assistant's Office, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Pike Company Minutes/Qualifications re: Leigh Hall, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Leigh Hall Renovation Project GMP Phase I and II, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Leigh Hall -Plaque, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Leigh Hall - New Furniture, 2002-2005 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Leigh Hall - Dedication and Reopening, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Sprague -Plan/Renovation, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Stoeckel Hall -Plans, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - 320 Temple -Plans, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - DMAC Materials/ Minutes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Facilities Report, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Leigh Hall Move, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Leigh Hall Architectural Designs and Development (on side of box), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Leigh Hall Feasibility Study and Plans, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Facilities Information System (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - School of Music -Information, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Space Information and Building Plans for Areas Assigned to Music, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Sprague Hall Renovation, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Computer System for Concert Office, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - School of Music -line of reporting by Vinny Oneppo, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Memo To Faculty Re: Reopening of Sprague Hall, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - Faculty
  - Miscellaneous People
    - Davenny, Ward (Memorial Concert), 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Samuel, Harold (Music Archival Collecting: Some Anecdotes), 1999 April (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Norfolk
    - Norfolk Programs, 1941-1955 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Norfolk at Yale, 1941-1966 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Norfolk -Art and Music Shared Responsibilities, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 318 - 319)
    - Norfolk -Annual Report, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 321 - 322)
    - Norfolk -Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 324 - 329)
  - Music at Yale
    - Cassett Quartet (Quartet in Residence), 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Tokyo String Quartet, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Kumho Asiana String Quartet, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - YAC/Moscow Chamber Orchestra (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - The Arts: Reflections of Society (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Credo for a Century (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Texte und Kontexte (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - NPR Performance (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Management Counsel (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Center for Studies in Music Technology, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - DMAC Library, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 341)
  - Dean's Correspondence
    - R. Blocker, 1992, 1994-2005 (Box 7, Folder 342 - 355)
    - R. Blocker Bio, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Thomas Duffy Acting Dean, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - Trips: R. Blocker
    - Hong Kong and Korea, 1996 July (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Korea Trip and Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - China- Alumni Chorus, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 361)
    - London -Trinity College, 1998, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Honors
    - Artist Diploma, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 363)
    - Prizes and Awards, 2002 May (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - Certificate of Merritt Recipients, 1965-1991 (Box 7, Folder 365)
    - Honorary Degrees in Music, 1972-1998 (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - Commencement
    - Graduating Students, 2001 May- 2002 February (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - Commencement-Academic Costume Code and Ceremony Guide (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Commencement, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 369 - 372)
    - Draft -Speech for Convocation, 20007 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Commencement, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 374 - 376)
  - Alumni
    - Alumni Convocation, 1998 April 4 (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Alumni Convocation, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 378)
    - Alumni Fund, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - Alumni Fund Checklist, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Alumni Fund, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 381 - 382)
    - Alumni Reunion, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - ACCPAS, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 384)
    - Searches
    - Composition Search, 1997-1998, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 385 - 387)
    - Composition Position Application, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - Music History Search, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 391)
    - Philharmonia Search, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 392)
    - Philharmonia Search -Eminence Letters, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 393)
    - Philharmonia Search -R. Blocker Personal File, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 394)
    - Chamber Music Society Series, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 395)
    - Administration and Governance, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 396)
    - Strategic Planning, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - Faculty
    - Faculty Vacancies, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 398)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1995 September (Box 8, Folder 399)
    - New Faculty, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 400)
    - Faculty Schedules, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 401)
    - Faculty Class Schedules, Fall 2004 (Box 8, Folder 402)
    - Faculty Class Schedules, Spring 2005 (Box 8, Folder 403)
    - Standing Committees, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 404)
    - Steering Committee, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 405)
    - Faculty/Steering Committee, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 406)
    - Faculty/Steering Committee/Board of Permanent Members, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 407 - 412)
    - Steering Committee Memos and Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 413)
    - Faculty Memos and Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - Boards
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 415)
    - Board of Visitors, 1997-2004 (Box 8, Folder 416 - 422)
    - Board of Visitors, 2004 July 31 (Box 8, Folder 423)
    - Board of Permanent Officers Memos and Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 424)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 425)
    - Committee Minutes, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Correspondence
    - Dean Blocker, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - "M", 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - "N", 1995-2004 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - "O", 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 430)
    - "P", 1990-2003 (Box 9, Folder 431)
    - "Q", 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 432)
    - "R", 1996-2004 (Box 9, Folder 433)
    - "T", 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 434)
    - "U and V', 2003 (Box 9, Folder 435)
    - "Y and Z", 1998-2004 (Box 9, Folder 436)
    - Singapore Trip, 1998 March (Box 9, Folder 437)
    - Renaissance Weekend, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 438)
    - Other University Searches, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 439)
    - Message books, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 447)
- Records of the Dean, 1942-1965; Accession 2013-A-056
  Separated Materials
  Records for this accession have been transferred from MS 1853, Noss (Luther) Papers.
  Budgets and expenditures are open for research. All other records for this accession are restricted until January 1, 2040.
  - Budgets and expenditures
    - Budgets, 1947-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Expense reports, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Restricted files
    Restricted until January 1, 2040
    - Class averages for Selective Service Office, 1947-1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Class lists, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - College Examination Board test scores, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Fees-charges and tuition, 1942-1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Registration, 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Registration and class lists, 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Registration, 1955-1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)